Guide to the Cornell University Fine Arts Library records, 1872-1995.
Cornell University Fine Arts Library records, 1872-1995.
- Series VIII. New York Urban Planning
  - Ithaca Buildings-Center Ithaca, September 9, 1980-January 30, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Ithaca -Clinton Hall, April 26, 1985-October 19, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Ithaca Buildings-Clinton House, June 30, 1972-summer 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    These newspaper clippings chronicle the potential demolition, movement for restoration, and subsequent restoration of the Clinton House.
  - Ithaca-Collegetown, October 3, 1967.-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Ithaca-Downtown, including The Commons, June 5, 1974-March 13, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Milstein Hall, October 7, 20030 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca Buildings-Old Courthouse, March 5, 1970-September 12, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Ithaca Landmark Preservation Commission, November 14, 1973-May 11, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Ithaca-Route 96, December 20, 1986-March 18, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Ithaca Buildings-Station Restaurant, March 20, 1973-January 21, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Ithaca-Stewart Park, March 4, 1985 -October 9, 1986- (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Ithaca-West End, September 2, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Ithaca Buildings-West Village, February 4, 1972-September 20, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Lansing, August 12, 1972-December 2, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Newfield, October 25, 1972-February 27, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - New York State Historic Trust, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Nichols, NY, October 2004 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Rochester, November 1, 1982-June 29, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Saratoga Springs, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Series IX. Architecture and Design
  This series concerns subject-specific architecture and design. It contains promotional materials, articles, letters, guidebooks, and urban planning information.
  - Domes, 1967-undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Contains pamphlets advertising geodesic domes, as first introduced by R. Buckminster Fuller.
  - Fallout Shelters, February 1952-October 1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fast Food, July 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Contains a lawsuit transcript and various anti-fast food letters and articles.
  - Garden Cities (Great Britain), January 1957-July 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Italy-Guidebooks etc., 1948-1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)